<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>c:/Users/danaw167/Desktop/Tenshi mod/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>The Celestial</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>private</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>dont_submit</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Celestial</Tags>
		<Tags>Touhou</Tags>
		<Tags>Tenshi Hinanawi</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>
	
At her core, The Celestial is a hybrid Tank/Disruptor. Her heaven-forged body grants immense passive damage absorption, and she can draw attention to herself with ease. On the offense she unleashes devastating attacks with her divine sword and stones, sundering armor and sending formations reeling.

However, one must be careful. The Celestial is arrogant and excitable, prone to outbursts of reckless power. While this allows her to effortlessly swap between offense and defense, it can also leave her vulnerable at crucial moments. Managing her [b]Exhilaration[/b] is key to success.


[h1]Summary[/h1]
[b]This mod features[/b]
1 new class
Original art, animations, fx, and audio
4 Color palletes (plus eyeless versions of all palettes)
9 Trinkets (including CC, CoM &amp; [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1689234891]Sunward Isles[/url])
Fully unique barks
Recruitment events
&quot;Compatible&quot; with all languages
Translated for the following languages: English, Russian

[img]https://i.imgur.com/wA2Wx4z.png[/img]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/06YkMOH.png[/img]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/zUL1KLf.png[/img]

[h1]Anticipated Questions[/h1]
[quote][i]&quot;Are any other DLC or mods required?&quot;[/i][/quote]
The Celestial is fully functional even with no DLC or other mods installed. There will be no missing icons or text.

[quote][i]&quot;I equipped Sword of Unletting Soil/Calamitous Ultimatum, but it isn&apos;t on my skill bar, why?&quot;[/i][/quote]
Make her drink this.
[img]https://i.imgur.com/gKkLLA4.png[/img]
It is required for the Spellcard Uses system to funtion properly.

[quote][i]&quot;Do you plan to release a Black Reliquary patch?&quot;[/i][/quote]
If I am still actively modding DD when Black Reliquary is fully released, then I will make a BR patch for her.

[quote][i]&quot;Do you have plans to translate for X language?&quot;[/i][/quote]
I only know English, all other languages must be translated by volunteers. If you would like to volunteer to help translate this mod, please contact me on Discord.

[quote][i]&quot;Are you making other Touhou Class mods?&quot;[/i][/quote]
Yes! Feel free to join [url=https://discord.gg/PhwGZnu]The Gensokyo Crypt[/url] for info on my upcoming mods; or if you want to give feedback/report bugs.

[h1]Misc Links[/h1]
[url=https://discord.gg/bfFbBQtBN4]The Gensokyo Crypt[/url]: This is my &quot;workshop&quot; for mod development. I post mod project updates, take feedback/bug reports, and discuss design here.

[h1]Credits[/h1]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/mandjgoody505/]Threey[/url]: Character, Icon, FX, Trinket, and Comic Art
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/Rage_Halo/]Adon[/url]: Character and FX Animations
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/danaw167/]Mrglrgl[/url]: Project Lead; Code; Writing
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/Mr_19/]The Necromancer[/url]: Audio; GUI Art/Animation; Code Assistance
[url=https://store.steampowered.com/search/?developer=%E4%B8%8A%E6%B5%B7%E3%82%A2%E3%83%AA%E3%82%B9%E5%B9%BB%E6%A8%82%E5%9B%A3]Zun-Team Shanghai Alice[/url]: Original Character

[h1]Translation Credits[/h1]
[url=]Name[/url]: Russian

[h1]Thanks[/h1]
Thanks to everyone on Discord who tested Celestial, and helped me stay sane during her development.


[h1]Legal[/h1]
This not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios</ItemDescription>
</project>

